

EDUCATION

Reifen Punkt GmbH, Heilbronn, Germany, Germany, October 2013 Qualified Retraining to become a wholesaler

Holz - Hauff GMBH, Leingarten, Germany, Germany, July 2004 Qualified training as a warehouse management specialist

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced and self-motivated Account Strategist with more than 15 years of experience overseeing sales figures and new account developments. A strong leader with the ability to increase sales and develop strategies to retain customers. Adept in analytical thinking, strategic planning, leadership and building strong relationships with international business partners.

SKILLS

- Development of customer and Creativity, enthusiasm product strategies
- · Dynamic personality with a high level of self-motivation
- Excellent sales skills
- Confidential, representative and convincing appearance
- Analysis of new trends, market observations

- Excellent communication skills and organizational talent
- German Native or Bilingual Proficiency
- English B2
- Polish B1

WORK HISTORY

July 2022 - Current

Teleperformance - Account Strategist - Google Ads Products, Barcelona, Spain

- Implementation of creative ways to improve the German Agency relationships, tailor and share performance-enhancing suggestions, and upsell or promote other Google products.
- Providing strategic advice and help Agencies get the best ROI on their clients' advertising investment by working closely with them in a consultative role.
- Communication with Agencies proactively, via phone and email.

June 2021 - June 2022

Webhelp - HP - Sales Representative, Valencia, Spain

- Sales of HP products
- · Outbound and inbound calls
- Order processing
- Responded to customer requests for HP products

January 2019 - May 2021

Immervahr-International - Business Development, Milan, Italy

- Acquisition of new suppliers for wholesale in the food sector, all over Germany
- Development of the Business Strategy to increase sales in Germany region
- · Market analysis

February 2016 - December 2018

Rotas Integrated Labels Technology - Sales Representative, Treviso, Italy

- Acquisition of new customers
- Advice and sale of exclusive wine labels
- Sales area in Baden Württemberg, Franconia (Bavaria)
- Preparation of the sales calculations

January 2015 - January 2016

Senza Aqua AG - Key - Account Manager, Tägerwilen, Switzerland

- B2B Sales areas throughout Germany
- Acquisition of new customers
- Customer service for approx
- 250 customers

December 2013 - December 2014

Deutsche Vermögensberatung AG - Asset Advisor, Heilbronn, Germany

- Acquisition of new customers
- Credit and Insurance brokerage

February 2010 - October 2013

Reifen Punkt GmbH - Institution, Heilbronn, Germany

- Increased sales by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.
- Increased sales by offering consultation on products and services and applying customer service and upselling techniques.

September 2004 - January 2010

Holz-Hauff GMBH - Warehouse Logistics Specialist, Leingarten, Germany

- Stock management
- Order processing
- Order picking
- Receipt and issue of goods